https://www.sabrered.com/sabre-privacy-policy

Skip to main content Due to COVID-19, we are currently out of stock on some products & response times are longer than usual.Read MoreDue to COVID-19 and the increased demand for consumer personal safety products, our service levels have suffered. We are working around the clock to catch up and provide assistance to your most frequently asked questions (FAQ can be found here). In addition, inventory levels are also limited due to this increased consumer demand for personal safety products. Please know our team is working hard to help keep you and your family safe during these unprecedented times. You can still find SABRE personal safety products online and in-store at your neighborhood drugstore, sporting goods, automotive, hardware, Army-Navy supply, or mom-and-pop convenience store. Click here to see a list of retailers. If you have placed an order recently, please know we are doing everything we can to maintain shipping schedules. We currently expect most orders to be processed with a 7 to 10-day delay. Thank you for your understanding, patience, and continued support of our essential workers!Read Less United States United Kingdom Login Create Account
Pepper Spray On the Go Seniors Athletic Home Defense Students & Parents Inert Pepper Sprays Tactical Products Supporting Charity Formulations Which Formulation Should I Use? Stun Guns & Personal Alarms Personal Security Alarms Stun Guns Bear & Dog Sprays Bear Spray Dog Spray Home Security Systems & Products Wireless Home Security Standalone Alarms Personal Safety Training Find an Instructor Become an Instructor Civilian Safety Awareness Program Civilian Safety Awareness Program Curriculum Instructors - Civilian Safety Awareness Program College Safety Program College Safety Program Curriculum Schedule a Campus Visit International Customers
Fulltext search
Apply
Pepper Spray On the Go Seniors Athletic Home Defense Students & Parents Inert Pepper Sprays Tactical Products Supporting Charity Formulations Which Formulation Should I Use? Stun Guns & Personal Alarms Personal Security Alarms Stun Guns Bear & Dog Sprays Bear Spray Dog Spray Home Security Systems & Products Wireless Home Security Standalone Alarms Personal Safety Training Find an Instructor Become an Instructor Civilian Safety Awareness Program Civilian Safety Awareness Program Curriculum Instructors - Civilian Safety Awareness Program College Safety Program College Safety Program Curriculum Schedule a Campus Visit International Customers
Blog & News Catalogs Contact
Close
Home > SABRE Privacy Policy SABRE Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, University / school affiliation or attendance or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.How do we use your information? We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.To improve our website in order to better serve you.To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.To quickly process your transactions.To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)How do we protect your information?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.We use regular Malware Scanning.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to:Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.Third-party disclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Third-party linksGoogle's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.We have implemented the following:We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared.According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:On our Privacy Policy PageCan change your personal information:By emailing usBy logging in to your accountOthersWeb FormHow does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify you via email:      • Within 1 business dayWe will notify the users via in-site notification:      • Within 1 business dayWe also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.Send you additional information related to your product and/or service.Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at:      • Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.Contacting usIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.SabreRed.cominfo@SabreRed.com800-325-9568Last Edited on May 26, 2017.
WARNING: Don't be fooled by our competitors' misleading numbers! Get the facts on heat, strength and the law!
Shop Pepper Sprays On The Go Athletic Home Defense Tactical Inert Pepper Sprays Students & Parents Seniors NBCF Products Shop More Protection Stun Guns Personal Alarms Bear Sprays Dog Sprays Wireless Home Security Standalone Home Alarms Who Is SABRE? Who We Are How We Perform How We Do It Work with Us Where to Buy Where We Came from How We Care Testimonials Careers Sitemap FAQ
Stay Informed, Stay SafeSABRE's newsletter is full of content to help you live a safe and healthy life. Enter your email to subscribe! Email * Leave this field blankSign-Up Twitter Facebook YouTube Instagram Footer: Center Content AreaMore than $2 million donated.Since 2008, SABRE’s pink product line has funded the equivalent of 20,000 mammograms.Shop our NBCF products.Footer: Right Content Area
Customer Service Store Policies Privacy Policy Copyright © 2005-2020 SABRE - Security Equipment Corp.
LE Instructor Login PSA Instructor Login
